export const JsQuizData = [
  {
      question: "Javascript is a ____ language",
      options: ["object-oriented", "object-based", "procedural","none of the above"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript? ",
    options: ["var", "let", "both A and B","none of the above"],
  answer: 1
},
{
  question: " Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
  options: ["getElementbyId()", "getElementsByClassname", "both A and B","none of the above"],
answer: 3
},
{
  question: "What is the use of the <noscript> tag in Javascript?",
  options: ["The contents are displayed by non JS-based browsers", "clears all the cookies and caches", "both A and B","none of the above"],
answer: 1
},
{
  question: "What does the `toLocateString()` method do in JS?",
  options: ["returns a localised object representation", "returns a parsed string", "returns a localized string","none of the above"],
   answer: 3
},
{
  question: "The process in which an object or data structure is translated into a format suitable for transferral over a network, or storage is called?",
  options: ["Object Serialization", "Object Encapsulation", "Object Inheritance","none of the above"],
   answer: 1
},
{
  question: "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
  options: ["stringify()", "parse()", "convert()","none of the above"],
   answer: 1
},
{
  question: "The 3 basic object attributes in Javascript are:",
  options: ["class,prototype,object's paramenters", "class,prototype,object's extensible flag", "class,parameters,object's extensible flag","none of the above"],
   answer: 2
},
{
  question: " What keyword is used to declare an asynchronous function in Javascript?",
  options: ["async", "await", "setTimeOut","none of the above"],
   answer: 1
},
{
  question: "How to stop an interval timer in Javascript?",
  options: ["clearInterval", "clearTimer", "intervalOver","none of the above"],
   answer: 1
},
];